(Sheldon:)No, of course not.
(Amy:)I trained Ricky how to smoke.
(Amy:)I can train him
to shoot a poison dart.
(Amy:)No jury would convict us
'cause people love monkeys.
(Sheldon:)I understand
(Sheldon:)the alcohol has stirred up
whatever it is
(Sheldon:)that makes girls go wild...
(Sheldon:)but I really need to talk
to smart Amy now.
(Amy:)Excuse me.
(Amy:)Have you considered
that your intelligence
(Amy:)might be the very thing
causing your dilemma?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Amy:)What do you think Ricky
over here would do
(Amy:)if an interloper
encroached on his territory?
(Sheldon:)Well, when challenged, monkeys
generally assert their dominance
(Sheldon:)through chasing, assault
and a stylized penile display.
(Sheldon:)That's a little outside
my comfort zone.
(Amy:)You're being too literal.
(Amy:)My point is, he would not meekly
surrender to the rules,
(Amy:)and neither should you.
(Sheldon:)Are you suggesting I play dirty?